[
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "A first-time client says they have Diabetes Mellitus. What would you have them do?",
    "options": {
      "a": "ask permission to contact their doctor",
      "b": "refer them elsewhere",
      "c": "have them get a prescription for massage a. ask permission to contact their doctor"
    },
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "A client has a Grande Mal Seizure during the massage. What do you do?",
    "options": {
      "a": "restrain or protect the client with pillows and time the length of the seizure",
      "b": "get them a glass of water",
      "c": "call 911 with pillows and time the length of the seizure"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "Massage therapists are not legally allowed to do which?",
    "options": {
      "a": "use battery-operated vibrators on clients",
      "b": "use electrical stimulation on clients",
      "c": "recommend exercises stimulation on clients"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "In the 5-element theory, which meridian is associated with 3- 5am?",
    "options": {
      "a": "LU",
      "b": "HT",
      "c": "LR",
      "d": "SP"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "Which meridian is associated with Tensor Fascia Latae?",
    "options": {
      "a": "LR",
      "b": "GB",
      "c": "ST"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "Where would you find the Small Intestine meridian? epicondyle of the humerus",
    "options": {},
    "correct_option": null,
    "correct_answer_text": "Medial"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "If you're palpating the vertebral border of the scapula, which muscle would you tend to work?",
    "options": {
      "a": "rhomboids",
      "b": "teres minor",
      "c": "infraspinatous"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "question": "When is deep abdominal work good for a client?",
    "options": {
      "a": "client is trying to lose weight",
      "b": "stomach cramps",
      "c": "client has an anterior pelvic tilt an anterior pelvic tilt"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "client has an anterior pelvic tilt"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "A woman on a treadmill at an 8% incline has pain in the buttocks. Which muscle is most likely affected?",
    "options": {
      "a": "gluteus maximus",
      "b": "quadratus lumborum",
      "c": "tensor fascia latae"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "Which meridian is associated with Autumn?",
    "options": {
      "a": "ST",
      "b": "LU",
      "c": "HT"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  }
]